Will your school be NEXT?
Rock 'n' Roll High School is a comedy, music film directed by Allan Arkush.
A group of rock-music-loving students, with the help of the Ramones, take over
their school to combat its newly installed oppressive administration.
Riff Randell, played by P. J. Soles.
Tom Roberts, played by Vincent Van Patten.
Eaglebauer, played by Clint Howard.
Kate Rambeau, played by Dey Young.
Miss Togar, played by Mary Woronov.
Mr. McGree, played by Paul Bartel.
Rock 'n' Roll High School is a 1979 American musical comedy film directed by
Allan Arkush, produced by Michael Finnell, and starring P.
Soles, Vince Van Patten, Clint Howard, and Dey Young.
The film features punk rock group the Ramones.
The film explores themes of rebellion, rock 'n' roll, musical, punk rock, bong.
The tone is lighthearted.